#### Contact

knowlesj07@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jodi-knowlesb9850362 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Customer Service Leadership

# Jodi Knowles

Registered Nurse Operating Room at Texas Health Dallas Dallas/Fort Worth Area

### Summary

I have 7+ years experience as a registered nurse in the operating room. My role is to provide excellent patient care as a circulating or scrub nurse by maintaining a safe environment during the perioperative experience. I have a background in the hospitality industry that provided a strong customer service base. My training after nursing school includes a nine month operating room specialty course provided through Parkland Memorial Hospital, one of the busiest level one Trauma hospitals in Dallas, TX. I worked various shifts for the next 3 years in all service specialties with a strong skill set in Orthopedics, ENT, Plastics, GYN, and Trauma/General surgery. I left Parkland to pursue a career in travel nursing with the hopes of expanding my knowledge base and give me insight to the variety methods of running an OR. My travels have included South Dakota, Florida, Colorado, New York, and multiple hospitals, and surgery centers in the DFW area. My travels have opened a new world of networking for me and has allowed me to strengthen my communication and relationship building skills. Working in a challenging environment such as the operating room provides me with the ability to adapt to difficult situations in any aspect of life with confidence. I am enjoying a travel life style as of now, but my mind is open to some different business opportunities. I am an extroverted, driven person with a passion to live up to my highest potential.

## Experience

Texas Health Resources
Operating Room Nurse
March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Dallas, Texas

Advanced Travel Nursing
Registered Nurse Operating Room
May 2016 - March 2019 (2 years 11 months)

I am an RN who Circulates and Scrubs a variety of surgeries in the operating room. I work contracts with various hospitals around the United States varying from 13-52 weeks at a time.

Parkland Hospital
Registered Nurse Operating Room
February 2013 - May 2016 (3 years 4 months)
Dallas, Texas

# Education

North Central Texas College Associates Degree of Nursing · (2008 - 2012)